http://www.dnews.com/site/privacy_policy.html

Submit
News tip/Upcoming eventLetter to the EditorObituaryWeddingEngagementBirthdayAnniversaryBirth
Local
Local
Top Story
Right hire, right time
As freshly minted University of Idaho Provost and Executive Vice President Torrey Lawrence begins his first few days in the position, the reaction to the hiring among faculty, staff and alumni has been decidedly positive.
More Headlines
Idaho legislators talk session expectations
WSU will change some grading because of COVID-19
Humane Society of the Palouse burglarized
Sports
Sports
Top Story
Cougs find another rally
PULLMAN — It wasn’t pretty basketball, and the stands at Beasley Coliseum were without spectators for the Battle of the Palouse’s 276th edition.
More Headlines
Cougs look to diversify their options on offense
Things get away from Bears in third quarter
Collier’s double-double helps No. 23 Texas women beat Idaho
Opinion
Opinion
Top Story
His View: Pandemic news is both good and bad
Good news is nestled among the bad COVID-19 news for the Pullman business community and residents.
More Headlines
His View: A charlatan’s disgraceful legacy of failure
Their View: Prioritize safety, invest in Idaho schools
Dec. 9 Letters to the editor
Obituaries
Life
Life
Top Story
Pilates in the pandemic
There are two new exercise instructors in Moscow, and their dream is to help people who experience chronic pain, are undergoing surgery recovery or just want better health.
More Headlines
Commentary: Things to consider when making raw seafood a part of your diet
Commentary: For a psychic, that’s some reach
Computers, just like their users, make mistakes, too
Business
Business
Top Story
New Gritman COVID-19 testing site open
Monday marked the opening of Gritman Medical Center’s new COVID-19 drive-through testing site on Jackson Street, southwest of Gritman in its overflow parking lot.
More Headlines
Test drive a fresh hairdo
Marketime Drug of Moscow to change locations this month
Brews, ’dos and hullabaloos
Events
Special Pubs
6-Day Index
E-edition
Subscribe
Search
Daily News Privacy Policy (www.dnews.com)This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.• To quickly process your transactions.• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.How do we protect your information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.We use regular Malware Scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to:• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.However, you will still be able to place orders.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third-party linksWe do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.GoogleGoogle's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.We have implemented the following:• Remarketing with Google AdSense• Google Display Network Impression Reporting• Demographics and Interests Reporting• DoubleClick Platform IntegrationWe, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.About Third Party AdvertisingWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our Services. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our sites or use of our Services and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness.Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer website.Google Doubleclick for Publishers (DFP) is an ad network partner that displays ads on our Services. To improve your ad experience on our sites and Services and elsewhere on the Internet, we may send non-personal information to Google DFP based on your browser's activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see is relevant to you. Google DFP also may use information regarding its own users to select which ads to display. Click here to learn more about Google DFP's ad practices, including how to opt out of using anonymous information to select which ads to show you.Opt-Out of CookiesIf you wish to manage or opt-out of cookies utilized by our site and third party advertisers, you can take the following steps:You may be able to download an opt-out cookie from the third party advertiser's website allowing you to opt-out of cookies. Please visit the third party advertiser's websites for more information.Your web browser may allow you to manage what cookies are accepted or declined. These settings can usually be found in the preferences or options menus of your web browser.Your web browser may also allow you to manually view cookies and delete the cookies you don't want or need. Check your web browser's settings for more information.Websites that require registration may allow you to opt-out of cookies. Check the account settings or preferences section of the website for more information.For more information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:• On our Privacy Policy PageCan change your personal information:• By logging in to your accountHow does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral trackingCOPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify you via email• Within 7 business daysWe will notify the users via in-site notification• Within 7 business daysWe also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Prohibited UsesThis Site is not intended for use by persons located within the European Economic Area (EEA). We do not request or accept personal information concerning or supplied by persons who are located within the EEA at the time they access this Site. If you have accessed this Site from within the EEA, you should immediately discontinue your use. If you have supplied personal information to us in violation of this provision, whether through the registration of new user accounts or otherwise, please contact us at webmaster@lmtribune.com.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.www.dnews.com220 E. Fifth St. Suite 205Moscow, Idaho 83843United Stateswebmaster@lmtribune.comLast Edited on 2017-02-17
Advertisement
Event calendar
Where you go for what you do. The region's best source for events, arts, culture ... everything.
Get me to 360!
Subscriber email options
Sign up to have headlines and breaking news delivered to your inbox.
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
Breaking News
Daily Headlines
You must select at least one email list.
Please enter a valid email address.
Sign up
Manage your lists
Sponsored Content
Ask a pro: Your go-to source for information from local professionals
Trending
What your neighbors are reading
Articles
ArticlesMoscow Chamber of Commerce Executive Director Jenny Ford to resignMoscow mask order extended to JunePaul Henry AbbottDog, supplies, thousands in checks and cash stolen from Moscow animal shelterPullman firm tests workers’ masks for virusPrichard Art Gallery shifts focusNorth central Idaho to receive 975 first doses of vaccine in DecemberMobile crisis response unit could launch in MoscowOvertaxed Idaho health facilities on brink of rationing careHilary Susan Lane
Webcams
Travel safe with road and snow reports
Go to webcams
Archives
Search archives for the Daily News and Lewiston Tribune here.
Go to archives
© Copyright 2020 Moscow-Pullman Daily News , 220 E. Fifth St., Suite 314 Moscow, ID | Terms of Service | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
